I sell white label media services to PR firms.
We've been stuck at 1.5 million for five years.
Agencies come to you.
Yeah.
They then white label your services
and sell your stuff to other people.
That's exactly right.
Do you have the same number of agencies
that are selling your stuff last year as this year
and the year before that and the year before that?
It's pretty high churn for the most part.
Are they churning because they're not using the articles
or because the articles are not good?
Because they're not using it.
You probably need a lower tier
that has some sort of usage component added on.
So it might be something like $1.99 a month
plus $100 per article.
You want to be low enough
that they don't churn on their bad months.
And so that's the fundamental issues.
I think that you're priced too high
for the majority of your customers
and too low for the ones
that you're going to maximize profit on.